gomage.com 2018-12-27

# GoMage - Privacy Policy

ECOMBIX Oy having a principal place of business at c/o Novius Pro Oy, Hitsaajankatu 6, 00810, Helsinki, Finland (hereinafter referred to as the “Company”, “we”, or “us”) collects from the individual user (hereinafter, referred to as “user”, “you” or “your”) certain personal data through the website [https://www.gomage.com](https://www.gomage.com/) (hereinafter, referred to as the “Website”).

This Privacy Policy contains Company’s policies and procedures governing the processing of personal data through the Website.

The processing of personal data through the Website is done in accordance with the data protection laws of Finland and EU.

By using the Website, you are hereby consenting to our processing of your personal data as set forth in this Privacy Policy. The term “processing” means any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

## Privacy Statement

We respect the privacy of our customers and adhere to high standards of protection of our customers’ personal data. Any personal data received by us will be used for the sole purpose of providing services to our customers.

## Types of Personal Data We Process

The Company adheres to data minimization principles. We process only minimal amount of information that is necessary for pursuing the legitimate interests of the Company. At the time you purchase software and/or services through the Website or register a user account on the Website, you will be asked to provide personal data, such as your full name, email address, telephone number and company information.

**IMPORTANT! THE COMPANY DOES NOT COLLECT ANY PAYMENT INFORMATION SUCH AS CREDIT/DEBIT CARDS, PAYPAL OR CHECKING.**

## Purposes of Personal Data Processing

The personal data collected by us will be used strictly for pursuing the legitimate interests of the Company namely: creating a unique customer account on our site, making payments for our modules and services with customer data, accounting reports of our company for purchases on our website, issuing licenses for the use of our products and for providing of other services requested by you.

If you provide your express consent in advance, we may use your personal data for direct marketing purposes (e.g., sending you our newsletter or offering services that may be of interest to you).

## Third Party Access to Personal Data

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal data to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal data to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish for this to happen.

In case third parties perform services (e.g., hosting of the Website) on behalf of the Company, the Company will assure that such third parties employ an adequate level of protection of personal data that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. You will be informed in advance if your personal data is transferred to the third parties i.e. before such transfer.

Your personal data may be accessed by the following third parties:

1\. The personal data provided by you for signing up for our newsletter will be used by MailChimp (https://mailchimp.com), which is a trading name of Rocket Science Group LLC having a principle place of business at 675 Ponce de Leon Ave NE, Suite 5000, Atlanta, GA 30308, USA, to provide you with the requested newsletter.

2\. The hosting services for the Website are provided by DigitalOcean (www.digitalocean.com) having a principle place of business at 101 Avenue of the Americas, 10th Floor, New York, NY 10013, USA.

3\. When you make payments through the Website using the Credit or Debit Card payment method, your payments will be processed by Stripe Inc. (https://stripe.com) having a principle place of business at 185 Berry Street, Suite 550, San Francisco, CA 94107, the USA.

4\. When you make payments through the Website using the PayPal payment method, your payments will be processed by PayPal Holdings, Inc. (https://www.paypal.com/) having a principle place of business at 2211 North First Street San Jose, California 95131, the USA.

5\. Customer relationship management assistance may be provided by ZenDesk Inc. (https://www.zendesk.com) having a principle place of business at 1019 Market Street San Francisco, CA 94103, the USA.

## Security and Confidentiality of Personal Data

The Company guarantees the confidentiality of any and all personal data supplied by the user when utilizing Company’s software or services and when visiting the Website. We do not disclose any user’s personal data to any third party unless ordered to do so by a court of law during the investigation of a criminal offense or as required under other provisions of disclosure of personal data.

The Company takes all necessary steps to safeguard your personal data including the use of specialized services to secure payment of all software or services purchased through the Website. All confidential information transmitted and received by us from the specialized services is encrypted with the help of software that uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL).

We will put reasonable efforts to maintain the security of and to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorized access, and modification of your personal data. However, please note that, due to the inherent risks of using the Internet, we cannot be liable for any destruction, loss, leakage, and falsification of personal data caused by circumstances beyond our reasonable control.

In the case of a personal data breach, the Company shall without undue delay and, where feasible, not later than 72 hours after having become aware of it, notify the personal data breach to the competent supervisory authority, unless the personal data breach is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of you.

You are solely responsible for keeping your login details in a private and secure manner.

## Links to Other Websites

The Website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave the Website, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Accessing, Correcting, and Deleting Your Personal Data

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal data in the following ways:

  * Whenever asked to fill in a form on the Website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes;
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at [support@gomage.com](mailto:support@gomage.com).

You may request to access, correct, and delete your personal data which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the personal data held about you or would like to correct, and delete your personal data please write to [support@gomage.com](mailto:support@gomage.com). We will answer your request as soon as possible but no later than within 1 (One) week. Your personal data also may be deleted by the Company if you withdraw your consent for processing of your personal data and inform the Company on it.

You have the right to receive the personal data concerning you, which you have provided to the Company, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from the Company.

In the case of deleting, correction or limiting the processing of your personal data, the Company will notify you accordingly.

## Children Using the Website

The Website is not meant to be used by children who are under the age of thirteen (13). If you become aware that your child(ren) has provided us with their personal data without your prior consent, please contact us at [support@gomage.com](mailto:support@gomage.com) for requesting us to destroy or de-identify such personal data.

## Jurisdiction

Your use of the Website is on your own initiative and at your own risk. You are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We do not represent or warrant that the Website is appropriate or available for use in any particular country or jurisdiction.

We are free to limit the availability of the website to a particular jurisdiction at any time in our sole discretion.

## Retention Period

Your personal data will be kept for as long as is necessary to provide you with the requested service. When your personal data is no longer necessary to deliver the requested service, the Company will delete it as soon as possible, unless retaining of your personal data is required by law for a certain period of time (e.g., for accountancy records).

## Submitting a Complaint

You have the right to submit a complaint about the way in which your personal data has been handled by using the contact details indicated in the Section “Contacting Us” which can be found at the bottom of this document. After you submit such a complaint to us, we will send you an email within 5 business days confirming that we have received your complaint. Afterwards, we will investigate your complaint and provide you with our response within a reasonable timeframe but no later than 2 weeks.

If you are not satisfied with the outcome of our response, you have the right to submit a complaint to your local data protection authority.

## How We Use Cookies

A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Generally, cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. With the help of a cookie, a web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic to our website and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## List of Cookies We Collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, allowing you to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency.  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your Customer ID with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AU | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID.  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer is allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
## Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support@gomage.com, or please write to the following address:

ECOMBIX Oy   
c/o Novius Pro Oy, Hitsaajankatu 6   
00810, Helsinki, Finland   
+358 9-424-562-39
